<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Lord of the P.I.G.S.</title>
    <description>Fast-paced simulation game for 4 players, where you decide the economic fate of the Republic of Meridia.</description>
    <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 23:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 23:47:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kickstarter is almost gone...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since the last post. Those days we were in the early days of a Kickstarter campaign.  The result was awesome, reaching the funding goal some hours before the deadline!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, we’ve been working closely with some of the backers and our design team to fulfill our Kickstarter commitments.  But now, we can say we have definitively sent the game for printing. Our partners in this first adventure will be AGR Priority, with long experience in producing board &amp;amp; card games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may think the adventure has come to an end… but this is just the beginning! Stay tunned for fresh news to come next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for following us :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/kickstarter-almost-gone</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/kickstarter-almost-gone</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good news: The Lords Go Global!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phew! The 1st week of our Kickstarter is over and it has been a nice one! We would like to start this 1st update with a big “thumbs up” for all the people that has checked out our campaign, and with a very special thanks to our &lt;strong&gt;BACKERS: Without YOU none of this could have possible&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To celebrate, we announce that Meridia’s Document Agency has started its presses! The Meridian Citizenship documents will be sent shortly to the first week backers, and with a nice surprise…They will be awarded a special title, that they’ve won on their own right: &lt;strong&gt;The Lordship of Meridia&lt;/strong&gt;! This honor is limited to the backers of this 1st week, as recognition and gratitude for their support. You are awesome!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/2014-12-lordship-cert-example.png&quot; alt=&quot;2014-12-lordship-cert-example.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, we have news regarding the rewards. After gathering info from our dear backers, we’ve realized that we were focusing the campaign too much on the EU and Spain… &lt;strong&gt;so we’ve decided to go global!&lt;/strong&gt; We have implemented two changes: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW REWARD – INTERNATIONAL KINGPIN (£35)&lt;/strong&gt;: This pledge gets you the Kickstarter version of the game with all the extra content just like the REGIONAL KINGPIN, but the difference is that it &lt;strong&gt;includes FREE shipping to ANYWHERE in the world&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have already pledged, and this new reward suits you better, you can switch to it through the “manage my pledge”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UNIFIED SHIPPING FOR THE PIGS&lt;/strong&gt;: We have unified the shipping for Portugal, Italy, Greece and Spain; &lt;strong&gt;shipping cost for all those countries is now £5&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These changes express our intention of making the game as affordable as possible to everyone around the world, regardless of the country they live in. Fun knows no frontiers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And last but not least, we’ve received inquiries regarding the possibility for a multi-copy reward so…introducing &lt;strong&gt;LAVISH COLLECTOR (£145)&lt;/strong&gt;, a reward that gets you &lt;strong&gt;5 copies of the Kickstarter version of the game with FREE shipping to ANYWHERE in the world&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have already pledged, and this new reward suits you better, you can switch to it through the “manage my pledge” option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s all for this 1st update. We hope that you will like the changes and we encourage you to get in touch with us for any comments, feedback or questions you might have. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/the-lords-go-global</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/the-lords-go-global</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lord Of The P.I.G.S. en català</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Per demanda popular, ara a més de tenir la web en anglès, castellà, italià i portugués, també en català!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/ca/posts/web-en-catala</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/ca/posts/web-en-catala</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lord of the P.I.G.S. Kickstarter Launches Nov. 26, 11 a.m. (CET)</title>
        <description>&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center; font-size: 150%; font-weight: bold&quot;&gt;
Big announcement!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After months of work and weeks of craziness, the moment has come.
Tomorrow 11 a.m. we launch the Kickstarter crowdfunding campaign for &lt;strong&gt;The Lord
Of The P.I.G.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/2014-11-pigs-heart-kickstarter.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/kickstarter-launch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/kickstarter-launch</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;First post on the website!
Not really relevant, just checking everything is working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; working, so let’s call it a day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/first/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.thelordofthepigs.com/en/posts/first/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
